question_data = [{"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The Mann Co. Store from Team Fortress 2 has the slogan 'We hire mercenaries "
                              "and get in fights'.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In 'Mario Kart 64', Waluigi is a playable character.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "There are 6 legendary cards in 'Clash Royale'.", "correct_answer": "False",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The game 'Battlefield 1' takes place during World War I.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Tetris is the #1 best-selling video game of all-time.", "correct_answer": "False",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In 'Sonic Adventure', you are able to transform into Super Sonic at will "
                              "after completing the main story.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Solid Snake is actually a clone from the DNA of Big Boss in the Metal Gear Solid "
                              "series&#039; history.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In Team Fortress 2, being disguised as a scout or medic results in a speed boost.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In the 'Half-Life' series, 'H.E.V' stands for 'Hazardous "
                              "Evasiveness Vest'",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Danganronpa 2: Goodbye Despair featured all of the surviving students from the "
                              "first game.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In the game 'Subnautica', a 'Spadefish' will attack you.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In Sonic the Hedgehog universe, Tails&#039; real name is Miles Prower.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Ana was added as a new hero for the game Overwatch on July 19th, 2016.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The end credits sequence in Grand Theft Auto 5 is over half an hour long.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "The Konami Code is known as Up, Up, Down, Down, Left, Right, Right, Left, B, A, Start.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In RuneScape, one must complete the 'Dragon Slayer' quest before "
                              "equipping Rune Platelegs.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "Several characters in 'Super Mario 64' blink their eyes, including "
                              "Mario himself.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "'Sonic the Hedgehog 2' originally was going to have a time travel system.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "In 'Need for Speed: Porsche Unleashed', the player can only drive "
                              "cars manufactured by Porsche.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                  "question": "'Resident Evil 7' is the first first-person Resident Evil game.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
